x-sense.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**How Do We Protect Your Information?** ****

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order, enter, submit, or access your personal information. We use a secure server for all supplied sensitive/credit information which is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and encrypted into our Payment Gateway Providers’ Database. The database is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights, who are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information will not be stored in our server. 

**Do We Use Cookies?** **  
** Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow). These cookies enable the sites or service providers’ systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. 

**Do We Disclose Any Information to Outside Parties?** ****

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or providing you with services, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also disclose your information when we deem that this is necessary to do so in order to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses. 

**Third Party Links** ****

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance** ****

We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only** ****

This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to any information collected offline. 

**Your Consent** ****

By using our site, you consent to our website’s Privacy Policy. 

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy** ****

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

Last Modified: 18/09/2018
